Thank you very much
Thank you for watching
Good morning, ladies and gentlemen.
Good morning, we are Kokoro
Good morning, we are Kokoro!
Nippon Sal, please take care of us.
Please take care of us.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
I love you!
Oh, my God.
That's sweet.
I love you.
I was collecting these for the Junkies' music video.
I was collecting cherry blossoms.
I'm used to it.
I'm used to being a rake collector.
Thank you for the rehearsal.
Thank you for preparing so much since yesterday morning.
We will do our best to have a good first day.
I look forward to working with you today.
Thank you very much.
Today is the first day of the first performance in Kobe.
My first time in Kobe.
I've been to Kobe before for handshake events and campaigns,
But this will be my first time at a live concert, so I'm really looking forward to it.
Is Kobe famous for croquettes?
Do they have beef? I'm looking for a caterer.
I'd like to eat beef.
You're at the Super Range again.
Did it get long?
It's gone.
Here!
It hasn't been a year yet.
I'm probably more nervous than I've been in about 3 years.
Here we go.
It's a Tim-cut!
It's my first show!
First unveiling?
Today.
I'm pretty sure I'm going to mess up these bangs.
I'm going to do it live for the first time today.
There's no delivery today, so it's challenge, challenge day!
I'll do my best.
Which talk is it?
I'm so excited!
I'm always in this kind of situation.
But I'm getting by.
I'll do my best.
To part my bangs or not to part my bangs.
I keep going back and forth.
I'm not splitting them now.
I'm not splitting these.
Do you want to essie it?
Like this.
You look like a pocket-hog gal.
But, you know, do you wash your bangs day and night?
If you're going to wash them, why don't you do them once for the gals, and then do them when you're cute at night?
That's right.
Twintails, right?
Twintails.
I want to wear twintails with my gal.
Gal pouty, daytime gal, nighttime pouty.
I'll open it.
I want to have a fan club moment with my fans.
I asked him if he liked the ones that didn't lose or the ones that did.
they were both about the same.
Well, great. I can see both.
So can I do both?
If you can.
I'll do it.
Okay.
I'll wear my hair cropped.
Hitomi, you've become the girl with the pats.
I see, I've become a woman with a slicked-back hairstyle.
Hitomi, tell us about your enthusiasm.
Enthusiasm?
This is my first time on the Lean Tour, and it seems like a lot of people will be coming.
I think it's important to start off with a bang. I'm so happy to be in Kobe, and it's my first time in Kobe!
I'm going to do my best with my voice.
Isn't she cute? He's nodding.
She's cute, you know.
He doesn't eat a lot of food.
Afterwards, there's Kobe beef waiting for you, I'm sure.
Hello. - Hello.
Hello.
I'm the slowest to get ready.
I'm already more prepared than anyone in Yamaoka.
Yes, sir.
It's black.
Don't eat, don't eat, don't eat.
Only black can win, only black can win.
preview of the next episode
делать
Thank you for watching!
Thank you for watching
I feel you as I sink into my belt
I'll be stronger tomorrow, and I'll end up innocent.
I'm tied to the slime, I'm sure it's virtual
I'll keep my thoughts to myself.
One second of your face, sober, blink and you'll be gone.
Wishes cut through just thinking about it, but I'm still not waiting for you.
Then miss my eyes.
Thank you for watching.
I'll hold on to you and won't let go.
I'm sure the other way has already passed.
I was so close, but I didn't know it.
Expectations and anxieties are in synapla.
I don't care if there's a lot of overlap
Peanuts, I want
me
me me
Its color changes, its color rises.
I finally get it I finally get it I finally get it I finally get it I finally get it I finally get it I finally get it
My youth is just beginning
Today is the first time I've ever dreamed of performing live in Kobe
I'm so happy!
Let's spend our youth together today!
Encore!
Why are you coming in here?
It's a secret.
Hey Hey, get together Hey Hey, secret dance
Hey Hey Hey, happy birthday to all of you
Tomorrow is Hana-chan's birthday. Let's celebrate together.
Happy birthday!
Have fun, Everybody
Today is my sweets sweets sweets sweets sweets
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop! I'm sorry, please stop!
Please stop.
Hana-chan Hana-chan
How old will you be on your birthday tomorrow?
Twenty-four.
No, 16.
Not 16.
Sixteen?
No, no, no, no, we have to make sure it's 24.
Look at this.
There you go.
Oh, my God.
Put it on, put it on, put it on nice.
That's nice.
It's good. It's good. It's good.
You got it.
I got it. I got it.
You're turning 24.
Left hand in two, right hand in four.
Here we go again.
From the beginning, princess.
From the end.
If we start from the beginning of the princess, we won't do it again.
Then, please play the song.
Yes, please.
I can't believe I'm staying up all night.
I'm interrupting a class.
I'm the star of the show.
I'm the host.
Today is our once in a lifetime
In a happy-loving stateroom
Play it in 1, 2, 3
My thoughts
I'm stretching so high
I'll only turn around, it's a big thought
I'll only be selfish once
I'll be with you forever 'cause it's another party
I won't forget today We'll still be friends tomorrow
Tomorrow I will be 24 years old!
I'd like to announce that I'd like to celebrate in such a wonderful way!
Yay!
Everyone in Kobe, Kobe Arisu is the best!
Thank you!
I just wanted to come back and see you all again.
Can I come and see you?
Thank you very much!
I will do my best to show you a more powerful
I'll do my best to show you a more powerful version of myself in the future.
I would be very happy if you could wait for me.
Thank you very much for your time today.
Thank you very much.
That's all for now.
This is Ribbons Love.
Thank you very much.
It's over!
There were a lot of firsts for me.
I was so nervous because it was my first show.
I'm glad that it ended without any major mistakes.
I'm very happy that it's over without any major mistakes.
Yes, the tour in Kobe is over!
I finished the tour in Mikkouen!
I want to go to Hyogo again!
I'll be waiting for you, Hyogo!
I'm off to eat Kobe beef!
Thank you for your hard work at Mitakaen!
Thank you very much for your hard work!
Everyone's power was really great!
I was so overwhelmed!
I cried a little before singing my solo.
Um...
Maika dashed all the way down the aisle to me...
I'm going to tear it off!
She said a lot of things to me.
I still felt like crying a little bit.
And when I saw the penlight, I was about to cry again
I tried to hold it in, tried to hold it in...
But then I started to blubber and blubber.
So I'm a little frustrated.
But the penlight was so beautiful!
Wow!
The blue and yellow were so beautiful!
Thank you for showing us your beautiful penlights!
I'll finish.
Oh, it wasn't on black now.
Good bye.
I'm off to have dinner with everyone!
Yay!
I'm celebrating my birthday tomorrow.
I was so happy to be able to celebrate my birthday one step ahead of you!
I was already in the groove!
Yay!
I was in high spirits!
It was so much fun!
Ochisami's applause
I'm so happy!
I was a little jealous that she always applauds me.
I felt a little envious.
Happy birthday!
Thank you so much!
Birthday Queen!
Your twintails look great on you.
And the birthday queen looks great.
And you look great on the piano.
The night show is over.
This time, because of the bigger scale of the show
We were able to put on a variety of performances.
New songs were performed for the first time.
There were a lot of people moving the microphone.
I think that thing is going to go boom!
I saw it in my dream.
I couldn't even stand up the microphone.
I thought it was going to fall into the audience.
I was shaking the whole time.
But I was able to do it during the show.
I think it was a good thing.
I hope you enjoy the rest of the concert as well.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for your hard work.
How was the Well performance?
I don't know if the Well performance went well.
I don't know if it went well.
I don't want to say it went well.
It's still a tour.
I want to keep progressing and improving.
With Tixia in everyone's heart
Bye bye!